# **Anuja Sanjay Chumbale**

Flat No.101, Bhatge Residency, Srushti Vihar Colony, Rohit Nagar, Bavdhan, Pune- 411021 PH: **7057879690**: anujachumbhale252@gmail.com

### Profile

I am a HR Professional, writer and a psychology student with interest in Training and Development and Psychometrics. I come with varied psychology related internship experiences. I love building relationships with people around me and helping them by channeling my organization and management skills into it.

#### Skills

- Psychometrics
- Development of Tools
- Employee Engagement
- Training & Development
- Research
- Module Development
- Planning and Execution
- Analysis and Creativity
- Relationship Management

## **Professional experience**

#### HR Intern

Thermax Limited, Enviro Division – Pune MH December, 2019 to Present

- At Enviro, I engaged in some aspects of Recruitment like Scheduling and Co-ordination of Interviews.
- I was mainly concerned with Joining Formalities, Induction and Onboarding, etc. I also assisted in PF and salary processing.
- I was also responsible for some strategizing and suggesting innovative implementable Employee Engagement Ideas.
- I also brainstormed Rewards and Recognition Activities and suggested for implementation in the organization.
- I also handled data for a project. I also engaged in designing of Presentation for a small presentation in Training and Development area.
- I designed a module for Emotional Intelligence. My internship project also had Assessment Administration on Working Styles and analyzing the outcome.

### HR Intern

Thermax Limited, Boilers and Heaters – Pune MH October 2018 to November 2018

- As a part of my job role, I contributed in Data Entry, Contributed to Recruitment and Learning and Development.
- I gained an understanding updating trackers, creating training calendars, conducting and managing training.
- My majority of the work included fixing appointments and lining up candidates for the interviews.
- I was also involved in maintaining employee records and was a core team member for employee engagement activities.

## Professional experience (continued)

### HR Intern Curtiss Wright, Pune MH May 2014 to Oct 2016

- It was an observational internship which involved attending interviews, inducting employees by conducting seminar on organisational policies.
- I learnt about the employee cycle, labour laws and POSH policies. I also undertook an
  assessment project where I assessed all the department managers on the Type personality
  tests.

### Education

Masters in Psychology- Human Resource Development and Management (May 2020), CHRIST (Deemed to be University)

Bachelors in Psychology (May 2018), Fergusson College Savitribai Phule Pune University

## **Technical Summary:**

 Proficient with Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint), Psychometric Tool Development

## **Accomplishments**

- Diploma in American Studies
- Counsellor at Step up Foundation
- Counsellor at Santulan De-addiction and Rehabilitation Centre
- Member of Centre for Academic and Professional Support (CAPS) Assessment Wing

### **Certifications:**

- Prevention of Sexual Harassment
- Tech Recruiter Certification
- Instructional Design for E-Learning (Pursuing)
- Cognitive Behavioural Therapy
- Testing and Tool Development Skills
- Nurturing Interpersonal Relationships
- Pune Model United Nations (2016 and 2017)

Interests: Cooking, Reading, Writing